{
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "What is a context in android ?",
            "answers": [
                "A - It is an interface to store global information about an application ",
                "B - It is used to create new components.",
                "C - Android has two contexts, those are getContext() and getApplicationContext()",
                "D - All of Above"
            ],
            "correctIndex": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "On which thread broadcast receivers will work in android?",
            "answers": [
                "A - Worker Thread",
                "B - Main Thread",
                "C - Activity Thread",
                "D - None of the Above"
            ],
            "correctIndex": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the 9 patch tool in android?",
            "answers": [
                "A - Using with tool, we can redraw images in 9 sections.",
                "B - image extension tool",
                "C - image editable tool",
                "D - Device features"
            ],
            "correctIndex": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "What is DDMS in android?",
            "answers": [
                "A - Dalvik memory server ",
                "B - Device memory server",
                "C - Dalvik monitoring services",
                "D - Dalvik debug monitor services"
            ],
            "correctIndex": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "In which technique, we can refresh the dynamic content in android? ",
            "answers": [
                "A - Java",
                "B - Ajax ",
                "C - Android",
                "D - None of the Above"
            ],
            "correctIndex": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "What is sandbox in android?",
            "answers": [
                "A - Each application runs securely in sandbox without interrupting another process ",
                "B - Android Box",
                "C - Android development tool kit",
                "D - None of the above"
            ],
            "correctIndex": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Why don't we give MIN SDK as 1 in android?",
            "answers": [
                "A - Android deprecated version",
                "B - There is no value for 1 ",
                "C - Android doesn't allow min version 1",
                "D - None of the above"
            ],
            "correctIndex": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "What is off-line synchronization in android? ",
            "answers": [
                "A - Synchronization with internet",
                "B - Background synchronization",
                "C - Synchronization without internet",
                "D - None of the above"
            ],
            "correctIndex": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Select a component which is NOT part of Android architecture.",
            "answers": [
                "Google",
                "Microsoft",
                "Facebook",
                "None of the Above"
            ],
            "correctIndex": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Which company developed android?  ",
            "answers": [
                "Apple",
                "Google",
                "Nokia",
                "Android Inc"
            ],
            "correctIndex": 3
        }
    ]
}